acorndomains.co.uk 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Acorn UK Domains Forum - Domain Name Forum UK

**Acorn UK Domains Forum - Domain Name Forum UK**

[Forums](http://www.acorndomains.co.uk/) Help >

**Privacy policy**  
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

**Privacy Policy**  
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

_(1) What information do we collect?_  
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:  
(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit, pages viewed and activity on each page);  
(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services (including subscription to our services, etc.);  
(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including details of your company, email address and contact details);  
(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including contact details, payment information, etc.);  
(e) any other information that you choose to send to us.

_(2) Cookies_  
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.  
We use both "session" cookies and "persistent" cookies on our websites. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and to monitor user behaviour for statistical and marketing purposes. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit;  
Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.  
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. View Google's privacy policy.  
Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

DoubleClick DART Cookie   
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.acorndomains.co.uk.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.acorndomains.co.uk and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Clickbank  
Amazon

_(3) Using your personal data_  
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.  
We may use your personal information to:  
(a) administer the website;  
(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;  
(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;  
(d) supply to you services purchased via the website;  
(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;  
(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;  
(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;  
(h) send to you our newsletter(s) and other marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications)  
(i) provide third parties with statistical information about our users - but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;  
(j) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;  
Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.  
We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.  
All our website financial transactions are handled PayPal. You should only provide your personal information to PayPal we will share information with PayPal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.  
_  
(4) Disclosures_  
We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.  
In addition, we may disclose information about you:  
(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;  
(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;  
(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and  
(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.  
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

_(5) International data transfers_  
Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.  
Information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United Kingdom, and the United States) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area.  
In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the Internet and may be available, via the Internet, around the world.  
You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

_(6) Security of your personal data_  
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.  
We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. The server is hosted and managed by a 3rd-party company as a paid service. We are fully reliant on their services and systems to secure our site and the data it contains.  
We take great care to ensure any confidential information remains protected, but we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the Internet.  
You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.

_(7) Policy amendments_  
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.   
We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

_(8) Your rights_  
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of an administration fee.  
You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

_(9) Third party websites_  
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

_(10) Updating information_  
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

_(11) Contact_  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to admin@acorndomains.co.uk or via the Contact Form on the site. 

**Acorn UK Domains Forum - Domain Name Forum UK**

[Forums](http://www.acorndomains.co.uk/) Help >
